bakugandimensions.com 2013-08-06

# PRIVACY POLICY | Bakugan

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THE SERVICE. At Spin Master Studios, Inc. ("Spin Master Studios") we are committed to maintaining the privacy, accuracy and security of your personal information. We have developed this website privacy policy to describe our privacy policies and practices and how we collect, use and disclose the personal information of those individuals who visit this website (the "Site") or use the services we offer thorough this Site ("Services").

Please take a minute to read this policy so that you understand how we treat your personal information. If you are unsure if or how this privacy policy applies to you, please contact our Privacy Officer for more information.  

## What is Personal Information?

For the purposes of this privacy policy, personal information is any information about an identifiable individual, other than the person's business title or business contact information when used or disclosed for the purpose of business communications.

For example, personal information includes your name, age, e-mail address, preferences (such as asking to receive our newsletters or special offers) and, where applicable, payment details.  

## What Personal Information Do We Collect?

You can visit the Site or use the Services without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself, including your e-mail address. Our web server may collect information related to your visit to the Site or the Services, including the IP address and domain used to access the Site or the Services, the type and version of your browser, the website you came from to access the Site or the Services, the page you entered and exited at, any pages that are viewed by that IP address and what country you are from. We use this information to monitor the Site's and Services' performance (such as number of visits, average time spent per page, number of page views) and for our business purposes such as working to continually upgrade the Site and Services.

In addition, we may collect the personal information that you submit to us, such as your name, address and any other contact or other information that you choose to provide by:

  * Registering as a member on the Site or for a Service;
  * Contributing an article, video or comment to the Site or a Service;
  * By corresponding with us via e-mail using the hyperlinks created for that purpose; or
  * Participating in surveys or polls, or respond to special offers, give-aways or promotions.

Your personal information may also be collected when you participate in surveys or polls, or respond to special offers, give-aways or promotions on the Site. In addition, the Site may store your electronic chat and other communications as a necessary incident to the transmission and delivery of those communications and to prevent misuse of our Site and Services. Other information, such as your account status, is created and maintained by the Site in the normal course of providing service to our members and other users.  

## Why Do We Collect, Use, and Disclose Personal Information?

In addition to the specific purposes that we may advise you of at, or before, the time that we collect your personal information, we may also collect personal information from you so that we may:

  * Establish, maintain and manage our relationship with you;
  * Enforce our Terms of Use, including investigating user conduct and, in some cases, banning a user temporarily or permanently from the Site or Services if that user engages in inappropriate conduct;
  * Review and improve the products and services that we provide to you;
  * Comply with your requests;
  * Protect us against error, fraud, theft and damage to our goods and property; and

  * Comply with applicable law or regulatory requirements.

We may also use your contact information to provide you or your parent(s)/guardian(s) with notification regarding the Site or Services, such as any future amendments to this policy, and may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's or other public agency's (including schools or children services) request or if we feel that such disclosure may prevent the instigation of a crime, facilitate an investigation related to public safety or protect the safety of a child using the Site or Services, protect the security or integrity of the Site and Services, or enable us to take precautions against liability.

Your personal information may be shared with our employees, contractors, consultants, affiliates and other parties who require such information to assist us with establishing, maintaining and managing our relationship with you or developing, operating and maintaining the Site and Services. In addition, your personal information may be disclosed or transferred to another party in the event of a change in ownership of, or a grant of a security interest in, all or a part of Spin Master Studios.

Further, your personal information may be disclosed:

  * As permitted or required by applicable law or regulatory requirements (for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena);
  * To protect the rights and property of Spin Master Studios;
  * During emergency situations or where necessary to protect the safety of a person or group of persons;
  * Where the personal information is publicly available; or
  * With your consent.

You acknowledge and agree that access to and use of this Site and the Services is provided via the internet and that your information, including personal information, may be transferred across national borders and stored or processed in any country in the world. We may collect, use or disclose your personal information without your knowledge or consent where we are permitted or required by applicable law or regulatory requirements to do so.  

## We may send you E-mail.

From time to time we may e-mail important information to you regarding the Site or the Services (such as a change to our service offering).

In addition, where you request information from us or become a member of the Site or any of the Services, we may use the e-mail address that you provide to send you information about offers on products and services that we believe may be of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive such e-mails, you may opt out of receiving same by simply telling us when you give us your personal information or register with us. If you later change your mind, you may easily edit your **"Account"** at any time to indicate that you now wish to, or no longer wish to, receive these messages.

If you have asked us to put you on an e-mail mailing list to provide you with certain information on a regular basis, you may ask us to remove you from the list at any time (using the unsubscribe instructions provided with each e-mail and on the Site or Service where you signed up).  

## Please Play Safe / A few words about On-line Safety

It is important to remember that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. In addition, whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information on message boards, in e-mails, or in chat areas on the Site or through the Services, that information can be collected and used by others. If you post personal information in public places, others may send you unsolicited e-mail messages or attempt to contact you in other ways.

Always be cautious about the information you provide or store online.  

## Special Notes about Children

Consistent with our obligations under various child privacy protection laws (such as the _Children's Online Privacy Protection Act_ ), we do not knowingly collect, use, disclose or store personal information of children under thirteen (13) years of age without their parent(s) / guardian(s) consent.

Accordingly, we request that children under the age of thirteen (13) not submit any personal information to us via the Site or the Services and obtain consent from their parent(s)/guardian(s) before accessing our Site or the Services. We request that children under the age of 13 not submit any personal information to us via the Site and require signed consent by means of returning a legal affidavit as required during submission of personally identifiable information from parents/guardians of children under the age of 13 to gain access to content and/or services on the Site. We require that all individuals accept our Terms of Use, which states explicitly that users of the Site and Service must have consent from their parent(s)/guardian if under the age of 13 years as well as prominently displaying a notice to parent(s)/guardian(s) to describe how we collect, use and disclose personal information. Where we learn that we have inadvertently gathered personally identifiable information from a child under thirteen (13), we will attempt to notify such child's parent or guardian and remove such information from our records.

If you are the parent or guardian of a teenager who is under the age of eighteen (18) but at least thirteen (13) years old, and have authorized your teenager to use your **Account** , we urge you to instruct your teenager to NEVER give out his or her real name, address, phone number or other personally identifiable information while using the Service. Teenagers under the age of eighteen (18) but at least thirteen (13) years old should encourage their parents to review this policy and to contact us if they have any questions.

If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under thirteen (13), please contact our Privacy Officer in the manner noted below.  

## How Do We Use Cookies?

When you visit the Site or Services, we may place a "cookie" on the hard drive of your computer to track your visit. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your hard drive through your web browser that can only be read by the website that placed the cookie on your hard drive. The cookie acts as an identification card and allows the Site to identify you and to record your passwords and preferences. The cookie allows us to track your visit to the Site or Services so that we can better understand your use of the Site and Services so that we can customize and tailor it to better meet your needs. For example, our cookies help us to learn about the usage of the Site and Services by helping us to track how many visitors we have, how often they visit various sections of the Site and Services, and their geographic location.

Most web browsers are set to accept cookies. However, on most web browsers you may change this setting to have your web browser either: (1) notify you prior to a website placing a cookie on your hard drive so that you can decide whether or not to accept the cookie; or (2) automatically prevent the placing of a cookie on your hard drive. It should be noted that if cookies are not accepted, you will not be able to access a number of web pages found on the website.  

## Your Consent is Important to Us

By using the Site or Services, we assume that you have consented to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as explained in this privacy policy.

In addition, you may change or withdraw your consent at any time, subject to legal or contractual restrictions and reasonable notice, by contacting our Privacy Officer **** using the contact information set out below. In some circumstances, a change in or withdrawal of consent may severely limit our ability to provide products or services to you. All communications with respect to such withdrawal or variation of consent should be in writing and addressed to our Privacy Officer.  

## How is Your Personal Information Protected?

Spin Master Studios endeavors to maintain physical, technical and procedural safeguards that are appropriate to the sensitivity of the personal information in question. These safeguards are designed to protect your personal information from loss and unauthorized access, copying, use, modification or disclosure.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while this Site and the Services strive to protect your personal information, we cannot warrant the confidentiality or security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.  

## What about Third Party Advertisements or Links to other Websites?

Our Site and Services may contain links to other websites that may be subject to less stringent privacy standards. We cannot assume any responsibility for the privacy practices, policies or actions of the third parties that operate these websites. Spin Master Studios is not responsible for how such third parties collect, use or disclose your personal information. You should review the privacy policies of these websites before providing them with personal information.  

## Updating Your Personal Information

It is important that the information contained in our records is both accurate and current. If your personal information happens to change during the course of our relationship, please keep us informed of such changes.

In some circumstances we may not agree with your request to change your personal information and will instead append an alternative text to the record in question.  

## Access to Your Personal Information

You can ask to see the personal information that we hold about you. If you want to review, verify or correct your personal information, please contact our **Privacy Officer** using the contact information set out below. Please note that any such communication must be in writing.

When requesting access to your personal information, please note that we may request specific information from you to enable us to confirm your identity and right to access, as well as to search for and provide you with the personal information that we hold about you. We may charge you a fee to access your personal information; however, we will advise you of any fee in advance. If you require assistance in preparing your request, please contact our Privacy Officer.

Your right to access the personal information that we hold about you is not absolute. There are instances where applicable law or regulatory requirements allow or require us to refuse to provide some or all of the personal information that we hold about you. In addition, the personal information may have been destroyed, erased or made anonymous in accordance with our record retention obligations and practices.

In the event that we cannot provide you with access to your personal information, we will endeavour to inform you of the reasons why, subject to any legal or regulatory restrictions.  

## Inquiries or Concerns?

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies, please send an e-mail with your questions or comments to [support@bakugan.com](mailto:support@bakugan.com) or by mail:

Community Management, Privacy Officer  
c/o Spin Master Studios, Inc.  
5890 Jefferson Blvd. Suite E  
Los Angeles, CA 90016  

## Application and Interpretation of this Privacy Policy

It is our policy to comply with the privacy legislation within each jurisdiction in which we operate. Sometimes the privacy legislation and / or an individual's right to privacy are different from one jurisdiction to another. This privacy policy has a limited scope and application. Consequently, the rights and obligations contained in this privacy policy may not be available to all individuals or in all jurisdictions.

Any interpretation associated with this privacy policy will be made by our Privacy Officer. This privacy policy includes examples but is not intended to be restricted in its application to such examples, therefore where the word 'including' is used, it shall mean 'including without limitation'.

This privacy policy does not create or confer upon any individual any rights, or impose upon Spin Master Studios any rights or obligations outside of, or in addition to, any rights or obligations imposed by applicable laws. **** Should there be, in a specific case, any inconsistency between this privacy policy and such laws, this privacy policy shall be interpreted, in respect of that case, to give effect to, and comply with, such laws.  

## Modifications to this Privacy Policy

From time to time, we may make changes to this privacy policy to reflect changes in our legal or regulatory obligations or in the manner in which we deal with your personal information. We will post any revised version of this privacy policy on the Site and we encourage you to refer back to it on a regular basis. This privacy policy was last updated in March 2010.
